Hello.
こんにちは
How old are you now?
今、おいくつなんですか?
It's 21.
21です
You're so young.
めっちゃ若いね
What do you usually do?
普段何してるんですか?
Are you a student?
学生ですか?
Usually, I'm going to blow off the cleverness of beer with students.
普段は、学生とビールのお利口をぶっ飛ばします
Is beer clever?
ビールのお利口?
Sports or something?
スポーツとかの、あれ?
Baseball or something.
野球とか
After all, you can only be a cute girl, right?
あれって、やっぱ、かわいい子しかなれないですか?
No, but there are some standards,
いや、でもなんか、基準ちょっとありますけど、
But there may be too many students.
でも学生さんが多めかもしれない
Yeah.
うん
It's true that there are many girls who are obedient to beauty pageants.
確かにミスコンとかオブしてる子も多いかも
Does it become a title?
なんか、肩書きになるんですか?
What are the benefits of beer?
ビールのお利口って
No, I'm just a little proud of my friends and men.
いや、友達とか、男の人とか、ちょっと自慢できるぐらい
You can be proud of it.
自慢できるよね
I guess he was good at beer.
ビールのお利口してたんだ、みたいな
What kind of costume are you wearing?
どんな衣装なんですか?
It depends on the beer, but it also depends on which side you go to sell it to.
ビールにもよるんですけど、 どっち側に売りに行くかによ
I will.
ります
For example, are you going to sell to a giant?
例えば、 巨人に売りに行くのか、
If I was going to Hanshin to sell, I would wear Hanshin clothes.
阪神に売りに行くのかで、 阪神側だったら阪神のやつ着るし、
If he was a giant, he would wear something like a giant.
巨人だったら巨人のやつ着たりもする
Uniform.
ユニフォーム
If it's a beer like Ebisu-san, they have an Ebisu costume.
エビスさんとかのビールだったらエビスの衣装があるんで、
It's a bit like a red brick color.
ちょっと赤いレンガみたいな色なんです
When you say beer is clever, is it baseball?
ビールのお利口って言ったら野球なんですか?
Baseball is destiny.
野球は運命ですね
I have a personal image of baseball.
私勝手に野球のイメージがあるんです
Well, that's right.
まあ、そうです
Do I feel the same way?
僕もそんな感じですか?
Yeah.
うん
That's nice.
いいですね
Isn't it everyone's dream to be a beer expert?
みんなの憧れじゃないですか、ビールのお利口さんって
However, the stairs are steep, so my legs are stiff.
でも、やっぱり階段とか急だから足パンパンになります
It's tough, isn't it?
大変なんですね
Is that what you're wearing? That's a tank.
かついてるんだっけ、あれ、タンク
I'm wearing it.
かついてます
It's heavy, isn't it?
重たいですよね
heavy.
重たい
I was wondering if you would do your best to buy it so that I can reduce it quickly.
早く減らそうって思って頑張って買ってくれないかなって思って
But if you do it with a smile like that, I'll buy it.
でも、そんな笑顔でやったら買っちゃいますよね
No, but I'm wearing a mask right now, so yeah,
いや、でも今マスクしてるし、 そうそう、
Everyone is wearing masks too.
みんなもマスクしてる
a little bit...
ちょっと...
Climbing the stairs while wearing a mask felt like I was going to the bathroom.
マ ス クしながら階段登ると、 しにいって感じだった
It's painful, it's heavy, but I'm still smiling and pulling you closer.
苦しいし、 重 いし、 や っぱり笑顔で引き寄せてるところも
Yes, there is.
あります よね
It's a shame.
惜しいですね
Even though it's so cute.
こんな可愛いのに
Is it quite fashionable?
結構おしゃれさなんですか?
But I kind of like One Piece.
でも、なんかワンピースが好きです
You can fall in love with just one.
1個で好きれるし
I think most of the things I own are one-piece dresses.
持ってるのワンピースが多いかな
But do you think it's a little hot?
でも、ちょっと暑いなって思うんですか?
hot.
暑い
It feels pretty warm.
なんか結構温かそうな感じ
It's true that the fabric is thick, but...
確かに生地しっかりめだから、 でも、
It's fluttering so it's cool underneath.
ひらひらしてるから下を涼しいし
Is he a pretty good guy?
結構いいやつですか?
It's Zara, absolutely.
ザラです、全然
I really like Zara.
ザラめっちゃ好きです
It's a good style, so you can wear it well.
スタイルいいから、着こなせるんですね、
See you then.
じゃあね
I just happened to wear something that felt good to me,
たまたま自分にいい感じにあったやつ着けたから、
Looks good.
よく見える
It looks great on you.
すごい似合いますね
please.
どうぞ
It's starting to get hot, and I was wondering if she was wearing something really nice.
暑出だし、なんか本当にいいやつ着てるのかなって思ったし
I'm glad he seemed like a nice guy.
いいやつに見えてたのよかった
What do you do on vacation?
休みとか何するんですか?
During my free time, I take care of my wancher and my cat.
休みは、ワンチャーと猫ちゃん飼ってるから、
I've been staying in town, getting wet and cooped up.
ずっとタウン濡れて、引きこもってます
Do you go out much or with friends?
あんまり外出たり、友達と?
Even if I go there often, I only go to the supermarket.
あんまり行ってもスーパーくらいしか行かなくて
Do you go out with friends?
友達と出かけたりとか?
But I'm going to the night pool for the first time next week.
でも、来週ナイトプール初めて行きます
Night pool?
ナイトプール?
I haven't been there yet, and my friend is looking forward to a night out.
まだ行ったことなくて、 友達がなんかキャンキャンのナイトプ
L, I thought it looked really Instagrammable so let's go.
ール、 なんか めっちゃインスタ映えするから行こうって
What are you doing?
何するんですか?
Night pool.
ナイトプールって
I think I'm going there to look good in photos.
映えに、写真映えしに行くのかなと
Are you doing something?
なんかやってるんですか?
I'll post pictures of myself on those SNS.
そういうSNSで、 映えを投稿したりとか
No, I feel like all I have these days is food.
いや、なんかもう、最近は全然食べ物しか、
I only give him food because he likes to eat.
食べるの好きなんで、 食べ物しかあげてないんですけど、
food and pets.
食べ物とペット
I don't have many Instagram-worthy photos at all,
全然、なんかインスタ映えするような写真あんまり持ってなくて、
I'll go to the bathroom next week.
来週トイレに行きます
I feel like a young kid these days.
なんか今時の若い子って感じですね
It's shiny and looks fun.
キラキラしてて、楽しそうですね
Enjoy the night pool.
楽しみ、ナイトプール
Do you feel like you're curious about a lot of things?
結構、いろんなことに好奇心を持ってやる感じなんですか?
Yeah, I'm not sure about things I've never done or been to.
うん、やったことないものとか、 行ったことないとことかは行
I thought, ``I'll give it a try anyway.''
って みたいな、 とりあえずやってみようかなとか
The camera is pointed at me like this,
こんなカメラ向けられてますけど、
Don't you feel nervous or something?
そんなでもなんか緊張とかしてないですか?
No, I am, but I had a little bit of alcohol earlier.
いや、してるんですけど、 ちょっとだけさっきお酒飲んだんで、
A bit of a machine.
ちょっとマシン
It has a friendly feel to it.
人懐っこい感じあるよね
But when I don't talk, my face gets a little stiff,
でも なんか喋らないと、 顔がちょっときつめだから、
I've been told that it's difficult to talk to someone.
話しかけづらいみたいな、 言われたことがあって
Because she's beautiful, I feel like I can't reach her,
美人だから、手に届かなそうな感じって、
Do you know what I mean by it being difficult to talk to you?
やっぱり話しかけづらいっていう意味はわかる?
I don't want people to say no and make people think I don't notice.
いや、って言われて、 気づらいと思われちゃうの嫌だなと思
That's it.
って
It feels expensive.
お 高い感じするもんね
I'll go talk to you about anything,
自分から何でも話しかけに行こうって、
Think and do your best.
思って頑張って
I work as a beer vendor and get tips.
ビールの売り子とかやってて、 チップとかってもらえるんです
mosquito?
か?
My friends and I support each other, even those who don't drink beer.
仲 良しさんとかからは、 ビールを飲まない人とかも 応援して
We also ask people to express their feelings of wanting to give something to us.
あ げたいって気持ちを込めてもらったりもします
I don't buy beer, but my friends are...
ビール買わないけど、 仲良しさんっていうのは、
Do you understand?
分 かるんですか?
I like baseball and go to baseball games, but I don't buy beer,
野球が好きで野球見に行ってて、 ビールは買わないけど、
If you always go to the giant side, you probably won't be born today.
いつもとても巨人側に行くと、 今日生まれましないだろうな
Or, I'm in this seat somewhere.
とか、 どころこの席にいるって、
I heard about it through SNS, so I thought I'd go to this seat and see if it was there.
SNS通して聞いたから、 どころこの席に行ったらいるかなって
When I thought about it, he started talking to me.
思 うと、 話しかけてきてくれたんです
She's a poster girl.
看板娘ですね
It's nice to know someone.
知ってる人がいると嬉しいですよね
In such cases, there is no one who will exchange contact information and secretly give it to you.
そういう時に連絡先交換で、 こっそり渡してくれる人とかいない
Is it?
ですか?
There are some people who have given it to me along with money.
お 金と一緒に渡してきた人はいますけど、
I said let's exchange normally on SNS,
普通にSNSで交換しましょうって言って、
I returned the money and we are now friends on Twitter.
お金を返して、 Twitterとかで仲良くしております
There is no such thing as an unmanned LINE.
無人LINEとかはないです
I've never replaced it before.
今まで交換したことはないです
Have you ever been asked?
聞かれたことはある?
I've been asked this before.
聞かれたことはあります
Is it no good?
ダメなんですか?
It's not bad, but if you start doing it all at once,
ダ メではないけど、 一回にやり出しちゃうと、
When someone else said it to me again, it made me think that I could exchange it.
他の人にまた言われた時に、 交換できるんだって思われて、
I'll be in trouble if someone talks to me,
話しかけられちゃったら困っちゃうから、
Just pour beer.
あ くまでもビールを注ぐと
Are you dividing it properly?
ちゃんと割り切ってる?
I'm splitting it.
割り切ってます
Do you have a boyfriend now?
今、彼氏さんとかいるんですか?
I don't have a boyfriend.
彼氏はいないです
Do you want to meet someone?
出会い欲しいとかないですか?
I think I want one, but when I get home I have a pet.
欲しいって思ってるけど、 家に帰ったらペットがいるから、
It makes me happy.
幸せってなります
That's a lot to say.
結構でも言いますよね
People who buy pets seem to be serious about it.
ペット買ってる人は本気をくれるみたいな
That's what you say.
言 いますよね
When I bought a dog,
私もちゃんとワンちゃん買った時に、
I hope it's fulfilling.
充実しちゃうとね
Mom and Dad told me.
パパとママに言われました
Why did you buy it?
なんで買っちゃったの?
why?
なんで?
If you say that, you'll never get married.
って言ったら、絶対結婚しないじゃん
You feel like a child, don't you?
子供みたいなふうに思うでしょ?
surely.
確かに
hey.
ね
That's what I said earlier.
って先に言ってきました
Hasn't it been quite a long time?
結構長いことはいないんですか?
boyfriend.
彼氏
I agree.
そうですね
when?
いつ?
I stayed there until I was 20 years old.
20歳になってから、 20歳になったぐらいまでいたんです
But it's already been about a year.
けど、 もう1年ぐらいは経ったわけですからね
scared.
怖い
Time has passed so quickly.
時間が経ったのが早いって
It's okay because you're still young.
まだまだ若いから大丈夫
I thought you said you were already 20 years old.
もう前20歳って言ってた気がしたけど
Do you want to hang out?
ぶらぶらしたいとかないですか?
Absolutely.
全然ありますよ
Are you a person with a strong sexual desire?
性欲強い方も?
When I had a boyfriend, I wanted to do it every day.
彼氏がいた時は毎日したい派でした
Will my boyfriend give me an answer?
彼氏の答えてくれるんですか?
That feeling.
その気持ち
I'll try my best to answer, but
答えようと頑張っておくれるんですけど、
It's tiring to do it every day.
毎日だとしんどいから
He was older, quite a bit.
年上だったんですよ、結構
Around people, older.
人回り、年上で
Because of that, there were days when I felt tired every day.
それもあって、毎日だとしんどいっていう日もあったけど、
But he tried to answer.
でも答えようとしてくれました
That's amazing.
すごいですね
Still, every day.
それでも、全然毎日
Every day, I might be able to get better at all.
毎日、私は全然うえるかも
That's nice.
いいですね
Pretty naughty.
結構、エッチな
I like being too close to each other,
あんまりくっついてるのが好きなんで、
You don't have to have sex, though.
別にエッチしなくてもいいんですけど、
That's how I feel when I'm with you,
くっついてるとそういう気持ちになっちゃうから、
I was like, ``Let's do this.''
なんだかんだ、しようよ、みたいな
Are you saying let's do it?
しようよって言うんですか?
I say let's do it.
しようよって言いますね
It's like, ``Let's do it,'' or rather, ``I want to do it.''
しようよって言うか、したいな、みたいな
Are you saying that correctly?
ちゃんと言うんですか?
Or something like that.
とか、ちょっとちょっかい出したりとか
But I'm embarrassed to say it, so I tend to blurt it out.
でも、言うの恥ずかしいから、ちょっかい出すのが多いかもし
Not possible.
れない
Is that a sign?
そう いうのがサインなんですか?
Even now, I'm giving out signs that I'm sure you'll notice.
今でも気づくだろうなってくらいのサインを出してます
I'm planning on putting it out.
出してるつもり
It's cute, if you imagine it.
可愛らしいですね、想像すると
This person also feels like a pet.
この人もペットみたいな感じですね
Can I take some pictures?
いろいろ撮ってもいいですか?
Your face is a little red.
ちょっと顔赤くなってますね
After all, it's alcohol.
やっぱりお酒
Please stand for a moment.
ちょっと立ってもらって
It's so cute.
めっちゃ可愛いですね
Who do you say you look like?
誰に似てるって言われます?
Who are you?
誰なんですか?
There definitely is.
絶対いるよね
Hizamanomi-san.
ひざまのみさん
It's gold blue.
ゴ ールドブルーって
They look similar.
似てるね
It's behind.
後ろだ
what up?
どうした?
It's being visited.
巡られてる
Do you understand?
分かります?
Is it getting shorter?
短くなれてるの?
I understand.
分かりますよ
Got it?
分かった?
Got it.
分かった
Do you also wear short ones when you play for the first time?
ぶり子するときも短いの履いたりするんですか?
It's short.
短いですね
Do you feel like you have pants that you can show off?
見せてもいいパンツみたいな感じですか?
Sometimes it sticks to clothing,
衣装にくっついてる場合もあるし、
Some children wear them separately, but
別で履いてる子もいるんですけど、
I'm hot and don't want to get excited, so
私暑いしモクモクするの嫌なので、
I'm wearing normal pants.
全然普通のパンツ履いてます
Do you wear things like this?
こういうの履いたりするんですか?
I don't wear them at all.
全然履いてます
Can I take a look at this?
こ っちちょっと見てもいいですか?
Can I just give you the skirt?
そのままスカートあげてもらってもいいですか?
How far?
どこまでですか?
all?
全部?
pants?
パンツ?
Make it the future.
未来にしてください
Have you never received time?
時間とか受けたことないですか?
I have time.
時間あります
Only once.
1回だけ
I've only been touched harshly once.
かつい触られたこと1回だけあります
train?
電車?
train.
電車
what up?
どうした?
At that time.
そのとき
When I was getting off, someone hit me from behind,
降りるときに、後ろからシュッってやられて、
I was shocked and thought,
シュッってやられて、 へえと思って、
Did you just touch it?
今触りました?
When I said that, she said, and she definitely touched it.
って言ったら、 って言われて、絶対触りましたよね
It ran away really fast, so I chased after it.
めっちゃガンダで逃げちゃって、追いかけたんですけど
So now you know who it is.
じゃあ分かったんだね、誰かって
Understood.
分かりました
An ordinary office worker.
普通にサラリーマンの人
It seems like it could be anywhere.
どこにでも居そうな
Did you touch my butt?
お尻触られたんですか?
In the middle of this.
この中のところ
We were friends and he gave me a swish, and it was through my clothes.
仲良くてシュッってやられて、 中は服の上からだね
From above the pants, swish it pretty deep.
パンツの上から結構深めに、 シュッって
I'm asking you to wear my underwear.
下着になってもらってる
difficult.
難しい
It's thin.
細いっすね
I also like cameras, so it's Puyo Puyo.
カメラも好きだから、 ぷよぷよです
Are you doing any exercise?
何か運動したりしてるんですか?
normally.
普段
I don't exercise.
運動はしてない
All I do is walk my dog.
ワンちゃんの散歩ぐらいしかしてない
Can you maintain it?
それで維持できるんですか?
I also go to a beauty salon once a week.
あと週に1回エステ行ってます
What is esthetics?
エステってどういうの?
send?
送信?
Sending is done by Ogusu's hands.
送信、おぐすの手でやってます
Is it effective?
効果あるんですかね?
I went there again today, but it hurt so bad.
今日も行ってきたんですけど、 めっちゃ痛いから、
I endure the pain, pain, pain.
痛い痛い痛いって耐えてます
It's a string, pants.
紐なんすね、パンツ
It's a little erotic.
ちょっとエロいっすね
I love string pants and have a lot of them.
紐のパンツ好きでいっぱい持ってるんです
Will it be eaten by pets?
ペットに食われたりしないですか?
Ah, but there's something like this, especially when it comes to cats.
あ、でもなんかこう、 猫とかは特にこう、
I like hanging out, so like this,
ぶらぶらしたの好きだから、 こうやって、
I'm coming.
ていってやってきます
cat punch
猫パンチ
I feel like I can touch it.
触れちゃいそう
For dogs, bring freshly taken off pants.
ワンちゃんは脱ぎたてのパンツとか持ってきます
Really.
め っちゃ
Like yay.
イエーイみたいな
Take it to bed.
寝床に持っていく
It still smells nice.
やっぱりいい香りがする
I like things that are taken off, like clothes.
なんか脱いだやつ好きですね、服とか
Please sit down.
お座ってください
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
Is there a female fleet?
女性艦隊とかあります?
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
But I wonder where.
でもなんか、 どこだろう
It's soft.
柔らかいね
But I'm probably a very sensitive person.
でもたぶんめっちゃ感じやすい方なんですよね、
perhaps.
たぶん
That's why I get wet so quickly.
だからめっちゃすぐ濡れちゃう
Isn't there such a thing as a sex fleet?
性艦隊っていうのはないの?
Eh, not really, pretty much everything already.
え、あんまり、大体もう全部
Especially here, I wonder where.
特にここ、どこだろうな
But I guess it's the ears and neck.
でもやっぱり耳とか首のとことか
What will happen?
どうされると?
Like the neck.
首とか
Huh, there's something around here, like a mouth.
え、なんかこの辺になんか、 口とか、
I can understand things like breathing.
息とかがなんか分かると
That's what I'm thinking.
な ーってなります
I'm fidgety.
そわそわって
Don't you feel much in your chest?
胸はあんまり感じない?
No, not at all.
いや、そんなことないです、全然
Sometimes I just need one drink.
一杯だけでいけちゃったりするときもある
If you sit and wait for 10, 15 minutes.
10分、15分とかずーっと待って座ってると
That's amazing.
すごいね
I'm having it developed.
開発してもらってるの
Ah, yeah, but maybe it's not about development.
あ、え、でも開発とかじゃないかも
I wonder if it was originally like that.
なんかもともとそうなのかな
It may not have been developed much.
あんまり開発してもらったとかはないかも
You have erotic breasts.
エロいおっぱいしてるね
It's gone.
消えてる
I'll lick it all off, everyone.
ぺろぺろぺろって舐めてくるぞ、みんな
Eh, I've never licked you so much, or been licked for so long.
え、あんまり舐め、 そんなにずーっと舐められたりとかしたこと
Maybe not.
ない かも
In that 15 minutes or so.
その15分とかで
Oh, no, it was like 15 minutes of being touched and being touched with my hands for a long time.
あ、違う、触られずっと手で触られたのが15分とかだから
I've never been teased much.
あんまり舐められたことない
Could you touch me?
触られていけたの?
It went well.
いけましたね
Very high level.
すごいレベル高い
I wonder if the level is high.
レベル高いのかな
You're warm.
あなた温かいね
How big are your boobs?
おっぱいいくつなんですか?
I got a D because I was a little overweight a while ago.
なんか前ちょっと太ってたんでDやったんですけど、
Now that I've lost some weight, I'm smaller.
今ちょっと痩せたら小さくなりました
It's C.
Cです
But it's really big.
でも全然おっきいね
Big areolas and erotic.
乳輪おっきいとエロい
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
It will become quite stiff.
結構硬くなってきます
If it got this hard, wouldn't it be quite difficult during school days?
こんな硬くなったらさ、学生時代とか結構大変なんじゃない?
Isn't it rubbing off?
こすれちゃってしない?
Ah, but when I was a child, I used to be a little bit lazy.
あ、でもなんか早め、子供の時とか結構ちょっとガパイ良くて、
I was a little chubby, so I put on a sports bra early on.
ちょっとぽっちゃりだったから早めにスポブラみたいなして
I did.
ました
But I'm sure something may have rubbed off.
でも 確かになんかこすれたりしたかも
Pint.
ピンッと
Try clasping both wrists behind your back.
両手首に後ろで組んでみて
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I could also see the skin on her face.
肌顔も見られたんで
It's embarrassing because it's so bright.
明るいから恥ずかしい
Have you ever done it in a bright place?
明るいところでしたことないか
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
It's too embarrassing.
恥ずかしすぎる
How can it be this beautiful?
いったいこんな綺麗になるんですか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然
If you eat ramen, you will become beautiful.
ラーメン食べたら綺麗になります
I like ramen the most and eat it a lot.
ラーメンが一番好きでいっぱい食べてる
So the sides are clean.
それで脇きれいな
No, it's so embarrassing.
いや、めっちゃ恥ずかしい
No, it's really beautiful.
いや、めっちゃ綺麗だね
Wait, wait.
待って待って
what?
何?
It's too embarrassing.
恥ずかしすぎる
Have you ever been stared at?
ジロジロ見られたことない?
No, no.
ないない
But it's really beautiful.
でもすごい綺麗だね
tickles.
くすぐったい
terrible.
やばい
Then, the liver body too.
じゃあ肝体も
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Normally.
普通に
I'm sweating.
汗かいちゃったよ
It's embarrassing to sweat and it's hot.
汗かくは恥ずかしいし、暑いし
I was sweating a lot after drinking alcohol.
お酒飲んでからめっちゃ汗かいた
That's a nice smile.
いい笑顔ですね
I want to sweat though.
汗かきたいけど
tickles?
く す ぐったい?
tickles.
くすぐったい
It's softer than your mouth.
口より柔らかいね
Is it soft?
柔らかいですか?
At the back.
後ろで
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
towards the back.
後ろの方に
Shall we go to the dark place?
真っ暗の方に行ってみようか
A little higher.
もうちょい上
Do you usually touch it yourself?
普段自分で触ったりします?
do not.
しない
How many times a month?
月に何回ぐらい?
When did you come back?
いつ帰ったかな?
Do you touch it with your fingers?
指で触るんですか?
I don't really feel comfortable with toys.
なんかおもちゃ、あんまり気持ちよくなくて
That's right.
そうなんだ
External teeth, middle teeth.
外歯、中歯
Eh.
えー
I just can't decide.
ちょっと決められない
I can't decide.
決められない
When you touch it with your fingers?
指で触るときは?
It's inside.
中です
Put your finger in?
指入れる?
Isn't it a little damp?
もうちょっと湿ってない?
It's so cold.
めっちゃ寒い
Easy to get wet.
濡れやすい
Do you get wet easily?
濡れやすいんだ?
Is love that much?
恋愛はそんなに?
No, it just feels good.
いや、普通に気持ちいいですよ
It looks beautifully full.
綺麗にいっぱいみたい
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れてる
Sorry it's so big again.
また広くてごめんなさい
It's already very damp.
もうすごい湿っちゃってるね
What will happen here?
ここどうされるの?
Do you like it?
好きなんすか?
What will happen?
どうされるの?
How do you like to be treated?
どうされるのが好き?
I can't believe I'm being touched over my clothes.
服の上から触られるなんて
I'm touching it directly.
直接触ってるし
Direct is more unsatisfactory.
直接の方が物足りない
Can I see something?
なんか見ていい?
It's really cold.
めっちゃ寒いですし
It's cold.
寒いですし
No way.
やだ
I'm dying of embarrassment.
恥ずかしくて死にそう
Are you about to die?
死にそう?
I'm about to die.
死にそう
Look here.
こっち見て
That's amazing.
すごいね
I want to die.
死にたい
Hitahitadamon.
ひたひただもん
Why is it so damp?
なんでこんなに湿っちゃうんすか?
It gets wet easily.
すぐ濡れちゃうんです
Don't play.
遊ばないで
Is this okay?
こ っちだったらいいんすか?
Better than Buntz.
バンツよりは
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗だね
Please spread it out properly.
ちゃんと広げてごらん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I asked her to spread her pussy with her hand.
手を通しておまんこを広げてもらって
I can see inside.
中見えるよ
Is it that embarrassing?
そんな恥ずかしい?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
The most embarrassing thing ever.
今までで一番恥ずかしい
Have you ever done something like this?
こんなことしたことない?
I've never done it.
したことない
If it's light, please spread it out a little.
軽くでいいか、ちょっと広げて
I want to see your shy face too.
恥ずかしがってる顔も見たいから
How much is a lot of beer?
ビールいっぱい、いくらなんすか?
Lots of beer.
ビールいっぱい
I just woke up.
寝上がりしたんで
Is it full?
いっぱいか
This is how wet my pussy is.
これ自分のまんこが濡れてるんだよ
I don't know.
わかんない
Do you understand?
わかってる?
I understand.
わかってる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Let's take a look inside.
中見してみよう
Pull both.
どっちも引っ張って
Can you move this a little?
これちょっと動かせる?
What does it feel like?
どんな感じを?
I put more effort into it.
力入れたり
Try it again.
繰り返してみて
At this rate, it looks like it's going to drip.
このままさ、垂れてきちゃいそうだね
Can I lick it?
舐めてもいい?
It's too embarrassing.
恥ずかしすぎる
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
why?
なんで?
Have you ever been there?
されたことあるでしょ?
Yes, but not much.
あるけど、あんまり
Love too much pussy.
愛 すぎたまんこ
Are you not interested?
興味してこない?